Breda:
Hello, Wayside Camera Club, Breda speaking.
Dan:
Oh, hello, um, my name’s Dan and I’d like to join your
club.。
Breda:
That’s great, Dan.
We have an application form – would you like to complete it over the
phone, then you can ask any questions you might have?
Dan:
Oh, yes, thanks.
Breda:
OK,
so what’s your family name?
Dan:
It’s Green – Dan Green.
Breda:
So – can I take your email address?
Dan:
Yes, it’s dan1068@market.com.
Breda:
Thanks.
And what about your home address?
Dan:
Well, I’m about ten miles away from your club in Peacetown.
I live in a house there.
Breda:
OK,
so what’s the house number and street?
Dan:
It’s 52 Marrowfield Street.
Breda:
Is that M-A double R-O-W-F-I-E-L-D?
Dan:
That’s right.
Breda:
… and that’s Peacetown, you said?
Dan:
Uhuh.。
Breda:
So how did you hear about our club?
Did you look on the internet?
Dan:
I usually do that,
but this time, well, I was talking to a relative the other day
and he suggested it.
Breda:
Oh, is he a member too?
Dan:
He belongs to another club – but he’d heard good things about yours.
Breda:
OK.
So what do you hope to get from joining?
Dan:
Well, one thing that really interests me is the competitions that you have.
I enjoy entering those.
Breda:
Right.
Anything else?
Dan:
Well, I also like to socialise with other photographers.
Breda:
That’s great.
So what type of membership would you like?
Dan:
What are the options?
Breda:
It’s £30 a year for full membership or £20 a year if you’re an
associate.
Dan:
I think I’ll go for the full membership, then.
Breda:
That’s a good idea because you can’t vote in meetings with an associate
membership.
Breda:
If I could just find out a bit more about you …
Dan:
OK.
Breda:
So you said you wanted to compete – have you ever won any photography competitions?
Dan:
Not yet,
but I have entered three in the past.
Breda:
Oh,
that’s interesting.
So why don’t you tell me something about those?
Let’s start with the first one.
Dan:
Well, the theme was entitled ‘Domestic Life’.
Breda:
I see – so it had to be something related to the home?
Dan:
Yeah.
I chose to take a photo of a family sitting round the dinner table
having a meal,
and, um, I didn’t win,
but I did get some feedback.
Breda:
Oh, what did the judges say?
Dan:
That it was too ‘busy’ as a picture.
Breda:
Aha – so it was the composition of the picture that they criticised?
Dan:
That’s right – and once they’d told me that, I could see my
mistake.
Breda:
So what was the theme of the second competition?
Dan:
Well, my university was on the coast and that area gets a lot of
beautiful sunsets,
so that was the theme.
Breda:
Oh, sunsets,
that’s a great theme.
Dan:
Yes.
The instructions were to capture the clouds as well – it couldn’t just be blue sky
and a setting sun.
Breda:
Sure, cause they give you all those amazing pinks and purples.
Dan:
Yeah – and I thought I’d done that well,
but the feedback was that I should have waited a bit longer to get
the shot.
Breda:
I see.
So the timing wasn’t right.
Dan:
Yes – I took it too soon, basically.
And then the third competition I entered was called ‘Animal Magic’.
Breda:
Well,
that’s a difficult subject!
Dan:
I know!
I had to take hundreds of shots.
Breda:
I’m sure – because animals move all the time.
Dan:
That’s what we had to show – there had to be some movement in
the scene.
I got a great shot of a fox in the end,
but I took it at night and, well, I suspected that it was a
bit dark,
which is what I was told.
Breda:
Well Dan – you seem to be really keen and we’d be delighted to
have you in our club.
I’m sure we can help with all those areas that you’ve outlined.
Dan:
Thanks,
that’s great.